Guide to the Abraham Aronow Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Abraham Aronow photographs.
1981-2009
WA Photos 488
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
3.65
(24 boxes)
Groups of photographs that document contemporary photographers, as well as individuals related to the study of photography, 1982-2007; street photography in the San Francisco Bay Area, circa 1981-2009; sites throughout the American West, 1982-2008; and portraits and views, 1982-2017.
Aronow, Abraham, 1940-
General note
Title devised by cataloger.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The bulk of the collection was purchased from Abraham Aronow on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2011.
Series III. Scenes from the American West, as well as Series IV. Portraits Acquired in 2012, are gifts of Abraham Aronow, 2012.
Series V. Portraits and Views Acquired in 2017, is a gift of Abraham Aronow, 2017.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Abraham Aronow (born 1940)
Abraham Aronow is a photographer and retired medical doctor. He chiefly focuses his photographic work on portraiture of photographers, artists, authors, musicians, scholars, scientists, physicians, and other people he admires.
Aronow was born in Brooklyn, New York, and raised in New Haven, Connecticut. He received his Bachelor of Science degree at Massachusetts Institute of Technology and his Doctor of Medicine degree at Harvard Medical School. After medical school, Aronow served as an intern at Bellevue Hospital in New York City, and as a commissioned officer in the United States Public Health Service. Since 1969, he and his wife, Alice Barney Aronow (born 1942), a clinical social worker, have lived in San Francisco, California. Aronow retired from medicine in 2007.
At ten years old, Aronow learned photography from his father, an amateur photographer. In 1981, while working at Ralph K. Davies Medical Center in San Francisco, landscape photographer Ansel Adams became one of his patients. Adams invited Aronow to a filming session attended by the surviving members of Group f/64 and other photographers. This began a decades-long project by Aronow to make portraits of prominent photographers and other figures.
Scope and Contents
Groups of photographs that document contemporary photographers, as well as individuals related to the study of photography, 1982-2007; street photography in the San Francisco Bay Area, circa 1981-2009; and portraits of individuals involved in the arts, letters, and sciences, as well as views in the American West, 1982-2017.
Each folder in the collection contains a single black and white photographic print or ink jet print, except where color photographic prints and/or two or more photographic print or inkjet prints are noted.
Arrangement
Organized into five series: I. Portraits of Photographers, 1982-2007. II. San Francisco Community Photographs, circa 1981-2009. III. Scenes from the American West, 1982-2008. IV. Portraits Acquired in 2012, 1983-1984. V. Portraits and Views Acquired in 2017, 1982-2017.
Documentary photography -- United States; Photographers -- United States; Photographers -- United States -- Portraits; Street photography -- California -- San Francisco Bay Area; California -- Pictorial works; San Francisco Bay Area (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; Photographic prints; Aronow, Abraham, 1940-
- Portraits of Photographers, 1982-2007; Series I; 1.3; (11 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Organized into three subseries: Photographic Prints 8 x 10 Inches and Smaller, Photographic Prints 11 x 14 inches, and Color Photographic Prints, 12 x 16 Inches.
  Scope and Contents
  Portraits chiefly of contemporary photographers, as well as individuals related to the study of photography.
  - Photographic Prints 8 x 10 Inches and Smaller
    - Arnold, Eve, 1994 September 24; 2 black and white photographic prints, 5 x 7 inches (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Bravo, Manuel Alvarez, 1986 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Caponigro, Paul, 1986 December 20; 2 black and white photographic prints, 5 x 7 inches (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Christenberry, William, 1991 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Citret, Mark, 1984 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Coke, Van Deren, 1984 March 6; 1 color photographic print, 5 x 7 print on a 8 x 10 mat (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Davidson, Bruce, 1986 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dawson, Michael, 2007 March 9; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Folberg, Neil and Joe, 1986 February 28, 1987 September 2; 2 black and white photographic prints, 8 x 10 inches, and 1 black and white photographic print, 5 x 7 inches (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
    - Gowland, Peter, 1985 March 22; 1 color photographic print (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Green, Nancy Klein, 2003 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Gutmann, John, 1985 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Hutchings, G., 1996 February 14; 1 color photographic print (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Kertész, André, 1984 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      General note
      2 subjects, second subject unidentified
    - Lavenson, Alma, 1985 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Light, Ken, 1986 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Light, Michael, 2002 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Mercado, Emilio, 1995 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Misrach, Richard, 1985 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Morris, Wright, 1992 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Parker, Olivia, 1986 June 9, 1982 August 2; 3 black and white photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 26-28)
    - Salgado, Sebastião, and Ruth Bernhard, 1993 September 22; 2 color photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
    - Sturges, Jock, 1990 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Tenneson, Joyce, 1990 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Tucker, Toba Pato, 1983 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Vishniac, Roman, 1984 October 30; 1 photographic print, 8 x 10, and 1 photographic print, 5 x 7 (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
    - Washburn, Peggy, 2003 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Weber, Al, 1985 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Witkin, Joel-Peter, 1995 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Photographic Prints 11 x 14 Inches
    In addition to photographic prints, 11 x 14 inches, this subseries includes photographic prints 8 x 10 inches in mats and mounted on boards, 11 x 14 inches
    - Aaland, Mikkel, 1985 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Adams, Ansel, 1982 August 2, 1983 June 21; 6 black and white photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 40-45)
    - Adams, Ansel, and Abraham Aronow, 1982; 1 black and white photographic print, 8 x 10 inches, in a mat, 11 x 14 inches (Box 2, Folder 46)
      Alternate title: Forays into photography
    - Adams, Eddie, 2003 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Adams, Robert, 1995 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Allard, William Albert, and dog, 1998 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Alpert, Michael, 2006 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Altman, Robert, 2003 March 19 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Armstrong, Frank, 2002 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Auerbach, Ellen, 1994 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Avedon, Richard, 1986 March 14 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Ayres, Chris, and Elizabeth Ayres, 1994 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Baer, Morley, 1983 June 22 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Baldessari, John, 1994 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Bell, Jason, 2002 May 16; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 58-59)
    - Benson, Harry, and dog, 1994 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Bernhard, Ruth, 1985 September 28; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 61-62)
    - Bloom, John, 1985 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Boubat, Edouard, 1989 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Bridges, Marilyn, 2004 September 13 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Burgess, Rebekah E. M., 2002 December 24 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Callahan, Harry M., 1984 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Cameron, Robert, 1994 January 26 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Camhi, Morrie, 1985 March 11; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 69-70)
    - Capa, Cornell, 1984 October 31 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Carucci, Elinor, 2006 June 16; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 72-73)
    - Casanave, Martha Pearson, 1984 August 27 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Citret, Mark, 1984 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Clark, Larry, 2002 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Collier, John, 1985 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Connor, Linda, 1985 May 14 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Dater, Judy, 1983 November 1, 1985 May 14; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 79-80)
    - Dawson, Robert, and Ellen Manchester, 1994 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - DeCarava, Roy, 1984 October 28 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Delano, Jack, 1994 March 26 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Demarchelier, Patrick, 2002 August 8 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Dexter, King, 1984 March 27 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Dingus, Rick, 2002 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Dresser, Rod, 1983 October 30 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Dusard, Jay, 1985 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Edgerton, Harold Eugene, 1983 August 31; 2 black and white photographic prints, 8 x 10 inches, in mats, 11 x 14 inches (Box 4, Folder 89-90)
    - Eggleston, William, 1998 October 8 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Eisenstaedt, Alfred, 1984 June 28 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Engel, Morris, 2002 August 5 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Enyeart, James, 2003 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Eppridge, Bill, 2003 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Epstein, Mitch, 2004 September 9; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 96-97)
    - Erwitt, Elliot, 1998 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Feininger, Andreas, 1984 June 29; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 99-100)
    - Felter, Susan, 1984 March 13; 1 photographic print, 8 by 10, inches mounted on a board, 11 by 14 inches (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Flukinger, Roy, 2002 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Fraenkel, Jeffrey, and Frish Brandt, 1998 July 9 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Freed, Leonard, 2003 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Friedlander, Lee, 1990 July 19; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 105-106)
    - Gagliani, Oliver, 1985 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Gandert, Miguel A., 2002 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Garnett, William A., 1984 October 12; 1 color photographic print (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Gibson, Ralph, 1984 June 28; 3 black and white photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 110-112)
    - Gilpin, Henry, 1981 August 6 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Ginsburg, Allen, 1994 June 16 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Gohlke, Frank, 2001 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Goldberg, Jim, 1983 November 1; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 116-117)
    - Goldberg, Michelle Dearborn, undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Goldberg, Vicki, 2003 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Goodrich, Mary, 2003 May 6 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Gould, Hal, 1989 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Gowin, Emmet, 1994 June 15 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Green, Herb, 2004 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Greenfield, Lauren, 2003 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Greenough, Sarah, 1998 October 10 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Griffith, Phillip Jones, 2004 September 14 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Gutmann, John, 1985 July 29 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Haas, Ernst, 1986 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Halberstadt, Milton, 1985 January 14 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Harding, Thomas, 1993 August 24 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Hartmann, Erich, 1984 October 29 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Heinecken, Robert, 1985 March 23; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 132-133)
    - Heisler, Gregory, 1986 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Holub, Leo, 1985 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Hutchings, Gordon, 1996 February 14 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Hyde, Philip, 1984 September 24 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Jacobi, Lotte, 1984 June 29, 1984 June 24; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 138-139)
    - Jay, Bill, 1986 April 9 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Johnston, Helen, 1984 October 19; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 141-142)
    - Jones, Pirkle, 1985 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Karsh, Yousuf, 1984 June 26; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 144-145)
    - Kashi, Ed, 1998 February 27; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 146-147)
    - Kenna, Michael, 1985 February 15 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Kenna, Michael, and Camille Solyagua, 2002 September 26 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Kennerly, David Hume, 1994 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Kertész, André, 1984 November 3; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 151-152)
    - Kismaric, Susan, 1998 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Klett, Mark, 1996 November 2 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Kratochvil, Antonin, 2003 September 16 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Krementz, Jill, and Kurt Vonnegut, 1994 November 10 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Kriz, Vilem, 1994 July 27 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Lee, Russell, 1986 June 3 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Leibovitz, Annie, 1985 July 25; 3 black and white photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 159-161)
    - Leifer, Neil, 1998 October 12 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - LeMagny, Jean-Claude, 2001 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Levy, Stu, 2003 April 12; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 164-165)
    - Liebling, Jerome, 1984 July 1 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Light, Michael, 2002 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Link, O. Winston (Ogle Winston), 1998 October 11 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Loengard, John, 1986 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Macauley, Cameron, Ira Latour, and William Heick, 2002 November 7 (Box 7, Folder 170)
      Alternate title: "The Triumvirate"
    - Maisel, Jay, 1998 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Mandel, Mike, 1994 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Mann, Sally, 1994 June 13 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Manos, Constantine, 2004 September 25 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Mark, Mary Ellen, 1981 August 4, 1981 August 6; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 7, Folder 175-176)
    - Marshall, Jim, 2002 July 23 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Mautz, Carl, 2006 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - McGrath, Norman, 2001 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - McKenna, Rosalie "Rollie" Thorne, 1994 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - McSavaney, Ray, 1982 August 3 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Mendelson, Pamela, 2002 December 24 (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Mercado, Emilio, 1995 May 21 (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Meyerowitz, Joel, 1984 June 27 (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - Mezey, Phiz, 1985 May 9; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 185-186)
    - Michals, Duane, 1985 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Mieth, Hansel, 1994 July 24 (Box 8, Folder 188)
    - Millea, Tom, 1984 May 24 (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - Miller, Wayne, 1985 April 22; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 190-191)
    - Milstein, Barbara, 2004 September 13 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - Modica, Andrea, 2003 February 26 (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Hattula, 2007 December 4 (Box 8, Folder 194)
    - Morath, Inge, 1994 November 13 (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - Morgan, Barbara Brooks, 1984 October 27; 1 color photographic print (Box 8, Folder 196)
    - Muench, David, 1994 February 4; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 197-198)
    - Murray, Joan, 1985 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - Mydans, Carl, 1986 June 5 (Box 8, Folder 200)
    - Naef, Weston J., 1994 May 25 (Box 8, Folder 201)
    - Nash, Graham, 2007 March 12 (Box 8, Folder 202)
    - Neimanas, Joyce, and Robert Heinecken, 1995 December 29 (Box 8, Folder 203)
    - Newhall, Beaumont, 1983 June 21 (Box 8, Folder 204)
    - Newman, Arnold, 1984 June 26; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 8, Folder 205-206)
    - Nickel, Douglas R., 1998 July 9 (Box 8, Folder 207)
    - Old, Toby, 2006 June 15 (Box 9, Folder 208)
    - Owens, Pam, 2003 April 11 (Box 9, Folder 209)
    - Palmquist, Peter E., 2002 December 24 (Box 9, Folder 210)
    - Papageorge, Tod, 1994 November 11 (Box 9, Folder 211)
    - Parks, Gordon, 1986 June 4 (Box 9, Folder 212)
    - Partridge, Roi, 1983 May 12 (Box 9, Folder 213)
    - Phillips, David, R., 2007 November 28 (Box 9, Folder 214)
    - Phillips, Sandra, 1994 April 7 (Box 9, Folder 215)
    - Piakowski, Nata, 1985 April 1 (Box 9, Folder 216)
    - Picker, Fred, 1986 June 11 (Box 9, Folder 217)
    - Plowden, David S., 2007 December 5 (Box 9, Folder 218)
    - Porter, Eliot, 1984 September 24 (Box 9, Folder 219)
    - Rogovin, Milton, and Anne Milton, 1994 November 14 (Box 9, Folder 220)
      Alternate title: "Buffalo Gothic"
    - Ronis, Willy, 1994 October 4 (Box 9, Folder 221)
    - Rosenblum, Naomi and Walter Rosenblum, 1994 November 9 (Box 9, Folder 222)
    - Rosenthal, Joe, 1998 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 223)
    - Rosoff, Susan, 1991 December 21 (Box 9, Folder 224)
    - Ross, Alan, 1984 March 14 (Box 9, Folder 225)
    - Satterwhite, Al, 2003 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - Serrano, Andres, 2001 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - Sexton, John, 1983 June 21 (Box 9, Folder 228)
    - Shore, Stephen, 2004 September 17 (Box 9, Folder 229)
    - Siskind, Aaron, 1984 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 230)
    - Smith, Henry Holmes, 1985 February 9 (Box 9, Folder 231)
    - Sommer, Frederick, 1986 March 16 (Box 10, Folder 232)
    - Stern, Phil, 1994 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 233)
    - Sultan, Larry, 1983 August 14 (Box 10, Folder 234)
    - Szarkowski, John, 1994 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 235)
    - Tice, George A., 1986 June 13 (Box 10, Folder 236)
    - Tractenburg, Alan, 1994 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 237)
    - Troispoux, Yvette, 2001 October 26 (Box 10, Folder 238)
    - Uelsmann, Jerry, 1985 August 15 (Box 10, Folder 239)
    - Van Cleve, Barbara, 2003 March 1 (Box 10, Folder 240)
    - Van Dyke, Willard, 1983 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 241)
    - Vestal, David, 1986 June 7 (Box 10, Folder 242)
    - Vignes, Michelle, 1986 February 10 (Box 10, Folder 243)
    - Von dem Bussche, Wolf, 2002 January 26 (Box 10, Folder 244)
    - Wagstaff, Samuel J., 1986 June 4 (Box 10, Folder 245)
    - Walker, Melanie, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 246)
    - Washburn, Bradford, 2001 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 247)
    - Weems, Carrie Mae, 2003 September 3 (Box 10, Folder 248)
    - Wegman, William, 1994 October 7 (Box 10, Folder 249)
    - Welpott, Jack, 1984 February 29 (Box 10, Folder 250)
    - Weston, Brett, 1984 August 27 (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - Weston, Charis Wilson, 1983 June22 (Box 10, Folder 252)
    - Weston, Margaret W., 1985 July 25 (Box 10, Folder 253)
    - Wilhelm, Carol, and Henry Wilhelm, 2007 September 14 (Box 10, Folder 254)
    - Winokur, Michael, 2003 July 31 (Box 10, Folder 255)
    - Worth, Don, 1984 June 5 (Box 10, Folder 256)
    - Zuckerman, Beatrice Ullrich, 1984 May 2; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 10, Folder 257-257a)
  - Color Photographic Prints, 12 x 16 Inches
    - Owens, Bill, 1985 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 258)
    - Teske, Edmund, 1985 March 23 (Box 11, Folder 259)
    - Weston, Cole, 1984 August 27 (Box 11, Folder 260)
- San Francisco Community Photographs, circa 1981-2009; Series II; 1.25; (7 boxes)
  Organized into two subseries: Photographic Prints 8 x 10 Inches and Photographic Prints 11 x 14 Inches.
  Photographs that chiefly depict street scenes in San Francisco, California, and other cities in the San Francisco Bay Area, including Alameda, Pescadero, Oakland, and San Gregorio.
  Occassionally a title applied by Aronow to a photograph involves word play or a purposeful misspelling related to the image content.
  - Photographic Prints 8 by 10 Inches
    Arranged alphabetically by title
    - "OWII", San Francisco, California, 1993 November 16 (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - Apparitions, Castro Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 262)
    - The Body Shop, Castro Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Branches and Birdtime, Market Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 264)
    - Brief Encounter, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 265-266)
    - Bright Eye, Laguna Honda, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Chiseled Features, Night Window, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 268-269)
    - Couple, Union Street, San Francisco, California, 1993 January 1 (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Ennui, Laguna Honda Hospital, San Francisco, California, 1984 December 14 (Box 12, Folder 271)
    - Enzo's Alley, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 272)
    - Fallen is Babylon, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 273)
    - Fantasy Window, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 274)
    - Fashion Statement, Street Fair, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 275)
    - Find It Here, Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 276)
    - Fine Day, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 277)
    - Detail, Fire Engine, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 278)
    - Fisherman's Wharf, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Fisheye Food, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Flower Child, Haight Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 281)
    - Flower Lady, Window Display, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 282)
    - Golden Face, Halloween, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Grave of Jesse James (I), Saint Anthony's Cemetery, Pescadero, California, 2008 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 284)
      Misidentified by Aronow. Gravesite of Corporal Jesse James Cole (1981-2006) in Mount Hope Cemetery, Pescadero, California
    - Grave of Jesse James (II), Saint Anthony's Cemetery, Pescadero, California, 2008 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 285)
    - Halloween Sisters, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - Heads, Muni Bus, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 27 (Box 12, Folder 287)
    - Hell Yes!, Poster on a French Facility. Market Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 288)
    - Homage to Lisette, Laguna Honda Hospital, San Francisco, California, 1984 December 14 (Box 12, Folder 289)
    - Homeless, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 16 (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Innovators, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 291)
    - Lady Friends With Pet Rabbit, Laguna Honda Hospital, San Francisco, California, 1984 December 14 (Box 12, Folder 292)
    - Leopard Lady, Halloween, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 293)
    - Melissa, Noe Street, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 294-295)
    - Mirror Image, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1997 June 15 (Box 12, Folder 296)
    - Nattering Nabobs of Optimism, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 297)
    - Outward View, Market Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 298)
    - Pals, 19th and Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 299)
    - Partners (II), 18th Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 300)
    - Pedicure, Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 301)
    - Pensive on the Muni, N-Judah, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 12, Folder 302)
    - Performers, Laguna Honda Hospital, San Francisco, California, 1984 December 14 (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - Plug Sitter, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - Posters, Oakland, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 305)
    - Powerhouse Street Fair, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 306)